http://www.hamptonresearch.com/privacy-policy-25.html

Products (current)
Protein Crystallization Standards
Support(current)
Crystallization Tips
Crystal Growth 101 Literature (current)
Hampton Research Corp. Privacy Policy
Hampton Research Corp. a California corporation is committed to safeguarding the privacy of our website visitors, customers and service users.
We recognize that your privacy is very important and take it seriously.  This Privacy Policy describes Hampton Research’s policies and procedures on the collection, use and disclosure of your information when you use the website and purchase products offered by Hampton Research, and tells you about your privacy rights and how the law protects you.    By using our website, you consent to our use of your information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.
Our Privacy Policy has been updated to conform to California’s Online Privacy Protection Act (CalOPPA) and the European Union’s General Data Protection Regulation(GDPR).  EU users who wish to be notified please ensure that your consent is duly acknowledged with us or else we will not be able to process your data for purpose of marketing.
Personal Data
What and how do we collect information about you?
How will we use the information about you and why?
Transferring your information outside of Europe
Security precautions in place about data collected
Profiling
Marketing
Access to your information, correction and deletion
Other websites
Complaints
Changes to Our Privacy Policy
A) Personal Data
What is personal data?
Personal data, as described in US privacy law and information security, is information that can be used on its own or with other information to identify, contact, or locate a single person, or to identify an individual in context.  We collect this data from you when you fill out a form or enter information on our site, which may include, but is not limited to the following: names and contact information (i.e. emails and telephone numbers); credit history and other transaction history.
B) What and how do we collect information about you?
We collect information about you when you fill in any of the forms on our website (i.e. sending an inquiry, filling in a survey, giving feedback, etc.). Website usage information is collected using cookies.
You agree that we are entitled to obtain, use and process the information you provide to us to enable us to provide our services and for other related purposes including, but not limited to the following: updating and enhancing client records; analysis for management purposes; carrying out credit checks in relation to you; legal and regulatory compliance; and crime prevention.
When submitting forms on our website we use a third-party software provider for automated data collection and processing purposes, the provider will not use your data for any purposes and will only hold the data in accordance with our policy on data retention.
Analytics
We use analytics to store information about how visitors use our website so that we may make improvements and give visitors a better user experience. Usage data, such as your IP address, geographical location, browser type and version, operating system, length of visit, page views and website navigation paths, as well as information about the timing, frequency and pattern of your service use may all be considered as part of Hampton Research’s analytics.
Cookies
Cookies are files containing an identifier that is sent by a web server to a browser and stored by the browser.  These files collect standard internet log and visitor behavior information, which is then used to track visitor use of the website and to create statistical reports on its activity.  You can set your browser not to accept cookies and the above websites tell you how to remove cookies from your browser.  Please note in a few cases some of our website features may not function properly.  These cookies do not store any personal information about you, such as your name and address.
IP addresses
An IP Address is a unique numerical address assigned to a computer as it logs on to the internet. Your IP address is logged when visiting our site, but our analytic software only uses this information to track how many visitors we have from particular regions.
Internet Based Advertising
We use various advertising services, and as such there are tracking codes installed on our website so that we can manage the effectiveness of these campaigns.  We do not store any personal data within this type of tracking.
C) How will we use the information about you and why?
At Hampton Research Corp., we take your privacy seriously and will only use your personal information to provide the services you have requested from us.  We will only use this information subject to your instructions and applicable data protection laws.  All personal data we receive from you will only be processed for the purposes of preventing crime or as otherwise permitted by law or with your consent.
We collect information on our website to process your inquiries and improve our services, and will also use this information to share updates with you about our services which we believe may be of interest to you.  However, we will notshare your information for marketing purposes with companies so that they may offer you their products and services.
Third-party disclosure
Our work for you may require us to pass your information to our third-party service providers, agents, subcontractors and other associated organizations for the purposes of completing tasks and providing the services or products to you on our behalf.  However, when we use third party service providers, we disclose only the personal information that is necessary to deliver our services and not for these providers to use your information for its own direct marketing.  Non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for advertising or other uses.
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your information unless we provide users with advance written notice. This does not include website hosting partners and other parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or serving our users, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release information when its release is appropriate to comply with the law, safety, enforce our site policies, or protect certain rights.
D) Transferring your information outside of Europe
As part of our website’s services, the information which you give to us may be transferred to countries outside the European Union (“EU”). For example, some of our third-party providers may be located outside of the EU.  Where this is the case we will take steps to make sure the right security measures are taken so that your privacy rights continue to be protected as outlined in this policy.  By submitting your personal data, you’re agreeing to this transfer, storing or processing.  Where our third-party supplies are in the United States, we have ensured that their services fall under the “Privacy Shield” whereby participating companies are deemed to have adequate protection and therefore facilitate the transfer of information from the EU to the United States.
If you use our services while you are outside the EU, your information may be transferred outside the EU to give you those services.
E) Security precautions in place about data collected
When you give us personal information, we take steps to make sure that it’s treated securely. Any sensitive information (such as credit or debit card details) you provide us with is encrypted and protected.
While we strive to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of any information you transmit to us, and providing us with any information is done so knowingly, voluntarily, and solely at your own risk.  As a result, non-sensitive details (such as your email address) can never be guaranteed to be 100% secure.  Once we receive your information, we make our best efforts to ensure its security on our systems. Where we have given (or where you have chosen) a password which enables you to access certain parts of our websites, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential.
In accordance with the Fair Information Practices Act, we will notify you via e-mail within one (1) business day in the event that a data breach involving your personal information occurs.
California Online Privacy Protection Act
California’s Online Privacy Protection Act (CalOPPA) requires all California-operated commercial websites to post a privacy policy. CalOPPA requires that any person or company that operates websites which collect Personal Identifiable Information from consumers to post a conspicuous privacy policy on its website stating exactly the information being collected and those individuals or companies with whom it is being shared. Under CalOPPA, you will be notified of any Privacy Policy changes on our website and can change your personal information anytime by contacting us directly at tech@hrmail.com.
more at: http://consumercal.org/california-online-privacy-protection-act-caloppa/#sthash.0FdRbT51.dpuf
According to CalOPPA, we agree to the following:
Users can visit our site anonymously.
Once this privacy policy is created, we will add a link to it on our home page or as a minimum, on the first significant page after entering our website.
Our Privacy Policy link includes the word ‘Privacy’ and can easily be found on the page specified above.
You will be notified of any Privacy Policy changes:
On our Privacy Policy Page
Can change your personal information:
By emailing us
By calling us
By chatting with us or by sending us a support ticket
How does our site handle Do Not Track signals?
We honor Do Not Track signals and Do Not Track, plant cookies, or use advertising when a Do Not Track (DNT) browser mechanism is in place.
Does our site allow third-party behavioral tracking?
Unless a DNT browser mechanism is in place, we, along with third-party vendors such as Google, use first-party cookies (such as Google Analytics) as well as third-party cookies (such as the Facebook cookie) or other third-party identifiers (such as heat mapping) on our website.
F) Profiling
We may analyze your personal information to create a profile of your interests and preferences so that we can contact you with information relevant to you. We may make use of extra information about you when it is available from external sources to help us do this effectively. We may also use your personal information to detect and cut fraud and credit risk.
G) Marketing
Occasionally, we will send you information about our services, which may be of interest to you.  We collect your e-mail address in order to send information related to your product(s), respond to inquiries, process orders and send updates pertaining to orders.  We will not use false or misleading subjects and agree to identify any messages as advertisements in a reasonable way. If you have consented to receive marketing and no longer wish to receive this information, you may opt out at any point by contacting us at tech@hrmail.com.  We will honor opt-out/unsubscribe requests promptly.  Likewise, if you object to processing your information in writing for direct marketing purposes, the personal data shall no longer be processed for such purposes.
H) Access to your information, correction and deletion
We want to make sure your personal information is accurate and up to date.  You may ask us to correct or remove information you think is inaccurate by emailing tech@hrmail.com.  You also have the right to object to any data processing as well as the right to data portability.
You have the right to object to the processing of your personal data.  The only reasons we will be able to deny your request is if we can show compelling legitimate grounds for the processing, or the processing is for the establishment, exercise or defense of a legal claim.
I) Other websites
Our website contains links to other websites.  This privacy policy only applies to this website so when you link to other websites you should read their own privacy policies. Hampton Research Corp. makes no representations herein regarding the protection of your privacy on any third party website.
J) Complaints
If you feel that your personal data has been processed in a way that does not meet the GDPR, you have the right to lodge a complaint with the relevant supervisory authority.
K) Changes to our Privacy Policy
We keep our privacy policy under regular review and we will place any updates on this web page.  This privacy policy was last updated on January 21, 2019 in accordance with the new GDPR guidelines.
If you have any questions about this Policy, you may contact us using the following contact information:
Hampton Research Corp.
34 Journey
Aliso Viejo, CA 92656-3317 USA
tech@hrmail.com
(949) 425-1321
Crystal NewsI love learning!
Tutorials, news, product updates and more
Keep Me Posted
Hampton Research, first in crystallization since 1991, developing and delivering crystallization and optimization screens, reagents, plates, and other tools for the crystallization of biological macromolecules, including proteins (antibody), peptides (insulin), and nucleic acids (DNA).
Products|
Gallery|
My Account
|
Contact Us|
Quick Order
Support
Privacy Policy|
Email Address:
Password:
Keep me logged in
Forgot Password | New user
Close
Sign In
